NO BOY NO CRY ore zenshin GO
no boy, no cry, I advance go!
shounen yo kiite kure
hey boys, listen up
ningen nante taishita mon ja nai sa
humans aren't such a big deal
ashita nante moui ranai kara
who needs tomorrow anyway
nigitta kobushi wo kakusu na yo
so don't hide your fists
fuan ni yume wo
you're not old enough
uri tobasu hodo mada oiborechainai daro
to sell your dreams away to uncertainty
shounen yo kokoro no jyuu no
hey boys, you're the only ones
hikigane wo hikeru no wa kimi dake sa
who can pull the trigger in your heart
subete no wakamono wa iitta
all the kids said
doushi yo mo naku kudaranai
we're living in this senseless, ridiculous,
kono subarashii sekai ni tattaima ikiteiru kara
awesome world right at this moment,
subete no wakamono wa iitta
all the kids said
subete no hontou to uso wo
don't forget every truth or lie
kesshite wasurete shima wa nai you ni
subete no wakamono wa iitta
all the kids said
shinu ni wa mosugiru darou
we're way too young to die
shiraketa tsura ga naranderu karappo no kono machi de
in this empty town lined with empty faces
subete no wakamono wa iitta
all the kids took off
kaze no nai kono yoru ni
into this windless night
nanika wo kaeyou to shiteru kara
because they want to change something
{Concluded in a
{Rain of Tears
By special...
By special
you meant that?!
I don't feel like I'm gonna lose.
Sasuke... you...
If they continue to be released
for a long period of time,
Curse Marks will progressively
eat your body.
When they have entirely
eaten you...
you will lose yourself... forever.
This body...
It looks like there's no time to waste.
I don't have any feeling
in my left arm...
That power you have...
seems to involve
some risks too, huh?
Did you know...?
That this place...
is called the Final Valley.
I think this is the perfect stage
don't you think... Naruto?
Oh yeah...
I said there'd be
no more talking, didn't I?
Well in that case,
how about we bring it to a close...?
This battle.
All our battles up to now!
Next for Team 7.
Uzumaki Naruto!
Haruno Sakura!
Yippee!
With Naruto...?
And Uchiha Sasuke.
Yippee!
With Sasuke...?
Try not to slow me down, loser.
You...!
But... but... but... you told us...
That's why they...
Aren't we a three-man team?
That's right! We three are one!
Hey!
Are you hurt?
Scaredy Cat?
Hey... are you hurt?
You are one of the ones
I want to fight.
Sasuke!
I want... to fight you too.
I don't want to see
any more deaths
of my precious comrades.
Summoning Jutsu!
I... will protect Sakura-chan!
What's so funny?
Nothing's funny!
I'm happy!
When I think I can finally
beat you here!
What did you say?!
Don't talk foolish you failure!
I'm not going to be
a failure forever!
Just bring it now!
Put on your headband before that!
I'll wait.
I don't need such a thing...
Just do it!
You wouldn't even be able
to put one wound on my forehead!
You're wrong!
I'm saying this is a testament
to fighting on equal terms
as a Leaf Shinobi!
Naruto!
Sasuke!
I'll win no matter what!
Don't flatter yourself!
Stop it!
And from this time onward...
Chidori!
Rasengan!
— Rasengan!
— Chidori!
This Chakra...
This isn't good!
Naruto...
I...
It's started to rain!
Will it erase the scent?
No problem.
We're already close.
This way.
Was I too late...?
Naruto!
Why did things come to this?!
This is Sasuke's...
I didn't make it in time...
please forgive me.
Naruto...
I know the kind of person you are...
You must have made
a desperate effort.
Sasuke...
That's my boy...
With me you're all
your father talks about...
You are my one and only brother.
I will continue to be for you...
a wall that you must find
a way to cross over.
Even if you were to hate me...
You are someone
who can obtain Mangekyo Sharingan
just like me...
However, on one condition.
Your closest friend...
The Final Valley...
To think that Sasuke and Naruto
would battle it out here...
How ironic...
Yeah...
When I look at
the flow of this water
it's as if I'm being confronted
by an eternal never-ending battle...
Just like the fate of the two people
depicted in these statues here
who founded the Village Hidden
in the Leaves...
Naruto and Sasuke,
as long as you both live...
You have to kill...
your closest friend!
I'm not gonna...
abide by everything you say!
I will get my hands on power
doing it my own way!
I will surpass you
Without fail!
The rain's... let up, hasn't it?
Yeah.
With that much rain
I won't be able to pursue
the scent anymore.
Naruto is more important now
than pursuing Sasuke.
Yeah.
It's gotten interesting, hasn't it?
Yeah...
hitotsu hitotsu omoidaseba
when I recalled the parts one by one,
subete wakatteita kigashite ita no ni
I felt as though I had understood everything
iroaseta kotoba wa
faded words
boku no sugu soba ni oite atta
which I kept so close to me
kotae no denai yoru to
speechless nights,
a hint of warmth,
hitokira no nukumori to
and this distant yearning for you
haruka kanata no akogare to
I live,
tada sore dake wo
simply repeating this cycle
kurikaeshi boku wa ikite iru
held in my two hands
kono ryoute ni kakaete iru mono
a droplet of time
toki no shizuku
softly clutching forgotten memories
sotto nigirishimete wasureta kioku
lost words
nakushita kotoba
I'll keep these thoughts...
kono omoi wa
I'm sorry.
I'm really sorry Sakura-chan.
I made a once in a lifetime promise
that I would bring Sasuke back.
But I'm not finished yet!
I'll fulfill my promise
no matter what!
Since that was what
I was always saying...
that I won't go back on my word.
That's my Ninja Way!
Next episode:
"The Promise That Couldn't Be Kept."